[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Joe, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Piers, I'm sensational.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What was going on that made you think, \"Some thing's not right here\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "``", "DT", "NN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "RB", "''", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "This whole issue that's been going on for the last couple of years, you know ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "You were disconcerted after all that hitting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Not that I might know it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "So when they discovered that you had gotten these brain cells which slowed down or being killed off, how would you describe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "I wouldn't say killed off because through the process that I've experienced, they regenerate it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 51, "question": "And do you personally feel better for this treatment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "You know, I was feeling pretty good ahead of time before ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "What game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Oh dear, it's even worse than I thought.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Who's going to win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "I wish I knew.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Should it make any difference to a great player whether it's a little bit cold or warm?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Maybe not the temperature when you a little bit cold.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "``", "UH", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What's your gut reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "My gut reaction is, \"Oh man, you know, that's not cool.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 109, "question": "But you weren't even favorites, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "We were 17 and 19 point underdog ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "My money's going to be in my pocket to use at the grocery store, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Do you resent the fact you had to pay for a drink and a meal in the city?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Are you sure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I think I can say that with some qualification, it will not be snowing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "How do you deal with issues like that on the peripheral (ph) of the actual game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "PRESIDENT & CEO, NY/NJ SUPER BOWL HOST COMMITTEE: Well, exactly how much of that really is myth versus reality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "But does that carry with it a responsibility to always conduct themselves to the best possible level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Yeah, I mean I think that there has to be a code of conduct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Jon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "But this is the media fanning an issue because it sells newspapers and it gets people to watch TV.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Are you blaming me jobless?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "No, not you personally, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "What is that thing you really want to talk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yeah, I like to see just, just speaking for me, I think everybody has got their point of view.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Finally, just very quickly, one word answer or two word answers, who is going to win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "The team with the most points.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Woody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peyton"]}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Where's your money at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, it's hard to get a bet against Peyton.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Who are you rooting for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Of course the Seahawks just because he wants to (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Dan, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Hi Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peyton Manning"], "LOCATION": ["Seattle"]}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", ":", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "And let's talk about the game on Sunday, who's going to win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, you know, I think it's going to be a close game because these two teams -- and the match up I look at is Peyton Manning having the great year's offense -- number one offense in league, number one defense in Seattle.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "However, I do know this, I know this Peyton Manning is massive like you and Russell Wilson, his quarterback opponent, is a tiny guy by comparison, right, by the look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peyton Manning", "Russell Wilson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "How much does that come into play in a Super Bowl if it's all (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, I think first all is the experience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "You know, this could be the great swan song or it could be a bit of a dance group for him, couldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "You know, I think he's going to continue to play either way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Yes, in London, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 330, "question": "But, how do you feel about never having won a Super Bowl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "You know what...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "You sit in your cabin -- low cabin at night and go what the hell happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I'll tell you what it does affect me though, is when I watch the Super Bowl, you know, I feel -- I looked at it and after the game is over and someone's holding up the trophies and I say, you know, I never had that feeling.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Do you actually start saying Hail Mary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "That's what the players called.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "It was really, really important, you know, but that's what the play -- the play was called.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Is he being a bit of a wusser (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I'm not going to answer that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Could you (inaudible) a lot of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "I wasn't...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Curt, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Good to see you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Do you agree with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruno Mars"]}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "More importantly where is Bruno Mars going to rank in the pantheon of great half time acts (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "RB", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I think Bruno Mars -- and I'm not joking about this, will be brilliant.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruno Mars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Are you (inaudible) to your opera, Curt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I've been to the opera.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Curt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 537, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Because as much as you can seat up close...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "You face the (inaudible) and look at women's legs, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "No, men too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "You have grossed -- do you know of this, in 10 movies, you have grossed worldwide box office takings of $1.5 billion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "I didn't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1.5 billion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "How do you think he's doing since we last met?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "You know, I love -- I love the president and I think he's doing good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Are you a football man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "And, you know, I like football.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Who's your team?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "You know what, I don't have a team, team but I like individual the players.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Did you ever play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "I played but I broke both of my wrists in practice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Yeah, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Crabtree"]}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Who was talking about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Mr. Crabtree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "IN", "``", "UH", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Isn't that why we watch football for characters to show passion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Yeah, you know, I guess he was in a moment because I think he's a great guy but that's a -- I think he -- he apologized and went there -- he probably went home and saw that and like \"Oh, that was too much.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin"]}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "And what do you think of Justin Bieber's problems alone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Well, you know, I met Justin a few times and he's a great kid.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "What advice do you give him about the real world of pitfalls certainly given the famous dad and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "Well, you know, I'll tell him, you know, I try to tell him that he could tell me anything and we could talk about anything because I know he's going to go through, you know, all the stuff that I've been through but I want him to handle it well, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Is fame cloud a corrosive drug in your experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "It's different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "I'll tell you a speech on the State of the Union and how it applies to you personally, Chris Tucker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State of the Union"], "PERSON": ["Chris Tucker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Do you think Barack Obama, being president, for five odd years now, did he made America more or less racist having its first black president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "You know what, I don't know, I don't know but I know he's such - he's doing such a good job to me because I think he's - because he does more - he does what he could do as president but now, he just have some morals in some certain things he stand for.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "Do you think he's found that the problem of being president is it's very hard to get the stuff you really want done done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "And you're in a war zone everyday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Do you remember working at Burger King?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "I remember doing -- yeah, cleaning at night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard Pryor", "Eddie Murphy"]}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 779, "question": "Who is the funniest person you've ever seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 780, "answer": "Funniest person I ever seen was -- you know, my family is funny but with far as entertainment, you know, Richard Pryor, Eddie Murphy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "Do you agree with that prediction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "It might be true, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]